>> Brian Holt: useReducer。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: useReducer.
如果你是雷德克斯的人你就会觉得自己在家
If you're coming from Redux,
you'll feel right at home with this.
如果你不来 Redux 你会在后面学习雷杜克斯
And if you're not coming from Redux,
you'll learn about Redux later.
所以你也会没事的
So either way, you're gonna be okay.
这里我有一个用 " 减速器 " 的例子。
So here I have this useReducer example.
它允许你做的就是改变这里的颜色。
And what it allows you to do is
change the color of this up here.
所以，如果我点击红色，就会变成红色。
So if I click plus red a bunch,
this will turn red.
如果我转向绿色就会变黄
If I turn plus green, it'll turn yellow.
如果我把它变成白色的，对吗 ?
If I turn that it'll
eventually turn white, right?
现在，这个国家有很多要跟踪的情况，对吧 ?
Now, this is a lot of state
to keep track of, right?
我必须为三个不同的事情跟踪更新者和设置者，对吗 ?
I have to keep track of updaters and
setters for three different things, right?
那是一种痛苦，对吧 ?
And that's kind of a pain to do, right?
如果我有一个能处理这些问题的功能的话
It'd be really nice if I had one
function that handled all these
比较相似的操作。
relatively similar operations.
这就是用 " 减少 " 对你的帮助
Well, that's what useReduce does for you.
所以 useReduce 是另一个钩子。
So useReducer is another hook.
如果您不熟悉术语缩减器，那么它意味着您可以使用的功能
If you're not familiar with the term
reducer, it means a function that you can
运行时采用旧状态，某种类型的操作，并返回到新的状态。
run that takes in an old state, some sort
of action, and returns to a new state.
这真的是一个减速器。
That's really all a reducer is.
它基本上只是一种具有特定呼叫特征的功能，好吗 ?
It's basically just a function with
a certain call signature, okay?
所以在这里用 Reducer I 赋予它实际的功能
So here with useReducer I
give it the actual function,
就是这里的一个减速器的功能
which is this one up here,
the reducer function.
然后我给它一个初始状态
And then I give it an initial state.
这个初始状态就是一切都是黑色的对吧
And this initial state is
everything is black, right?
>> Brian Holt: 请注意，这与 Redux 不同。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Do note that
this is different from Redux.
在雷德克斯的情况下你预料它会在第一次运行
With Redux, you expect it to run
the reducer on the first time,
这不是你的
this does not do that.
>> Brian Holt: 在此情况下，为其提供初始对象和
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: In this case,
you give it an initial object and
这就是你的工作方式
that's how that works.
好的，然后再给你两件事情。
Okay, and
then here it gives you back two things.
它让你回到了目标
It gives you back the object,
在这种情况下，商店的当前状态是一样的。
in this case,
the current state of the store as it were.
而我正在毁灭 r， g和 b.
And here I'm destructuring out the r,
the g, and the b.
然后它为您提供一个分派功能，使您能够将操作分派给
And then it gives you a dispatch function
which allows you to dispatch an action to
减速器。
the reducer.
你可以看到这些按钮，它调度 INCREMENT_R，
So you can see here all these buttons,
it's dispatching INCREMENT_R,
DECREMENT_R， INCREMENT_G， DECREMENT_G， right?
DECREMENT_R, INCREMENT_G,
DECREMENT_G, right?
我认为这是很容易阅读的守则。
This is, in my opinion,
quite readable code.
所以这是一个非常好的例子来使用 Reducer。
So this is a really good
case to use useReducer.
如果你在减速器里看看
And then if you look
down here in the reducer,
它以对象的当前状态为动作。
it takes in the current state
of the object, the action.
然后在下面的下面，它会返回状态，或者
And then down here at the bottom,
it returns the state, or
所有这些都是回归状态
all these actually return state.
所有这些都是物权转让他们创造了一个新目标
And all these are just object.assign,
they're creating a new object,
旧的状态然后就会覆盖整个河对吧
the old set of state, and
then it's overriding the r, right?
这辆 limitRGB 确保它不低于 0 或 255。
This limitRGB just makes sure that
it doesn't go below 0 or above 255.
好吧这就是这个
Right, that's what this does.
接下来的步骤就是向上和向下 50，对。
And then the step here is just
going up and down 50, right.
所以如果我点击这个，就会达到 50 %的红色，
So if I click this,
it's going up to 50 red,
100 红， 150， 200， 250， 255。
100 red, 150, 200, 250, 255.
有道理吗
Make sense?
这很像 Redux
It's very Redux like.
现在，这个，这个减压器，这个减压器，非常容易的测试。
Now, what's great about this,
this reducer, it's extremely easy to test.
你只要给它一个老的状态，一个动作，然后测试输出，对吧 ?
You just give it an old state, an action,
and then test the output, right?
这允许您测试数据变异。
Which allows you to test data mutation.
所有错误都是从某种意义上的数据变异引起的，对吗 ?
And all bugs arise from problems with
data mutation in some sense, right?
因此，如果你能测试这一点，并确保状态的突变顺利进行。
So if you can actually test that and make
sure that the mutation of state goes well.
这对你很重要
That's a big boon to you.
这就是 Redux 在我看来的优点
That's the whole advantage
of Redux in my opinion.
正如你想象的，这真的取代了很多时候
So as you might imagine,
this really replaces a lot of times when
你需要 Redux你可以用 Reducer ，对吧 ?
you need Redux, you can just use,
useReducer, right?
那么，如果要为整个应用程序执行该操作，会发生什么情况 ?
Well, what happens if you want to
do it for your entire application?
那么，您可以同时使用上下文和 useReducer 。
Well, you can use context and
useReducer together.
基本上是雷德克斯对吧
Basically Redux, right?
是关于同一件事的
It's about the same thing.
所以我不再多使用 Redux 了
So I don't use Redux as much anymore.
我还是会教给你的
I will still teach it to you so
你可以做出你想做的决定
that you can make whatever decision
you want to make about that.
但我认为背景和 useReducer 在很大程度上取代了它的需求。
But I think context and useReducer
largely supplant the need for it.